Full-Stack Designer



Loves <u>UI/UX</u>, <u>CSS</u>, <u>UX writing</u>, and <u>using data</u>. Specializing in <u>Design Systems</u> & <u>Conversion Optimization through research</u>. 15 Year career grounded in telling stories and persuading through design. Thrives making complex visions clear.

Seeking: remote, permanent, positive impact, large projects, mentoring opportunities.

EXPERIENCE

iMARKET SOLUTIONS

Designer 9/2015 - PRESENT

- Designed hundreds of lead-generating websites for contractors.
- Improved processes: helped establish a 3-day design turnaround, helped create & maintain pattern library, incorporated design critiques, and wrote internal best practices.
- 2 years as Design Team CRO Representative: AB testing, heatmaps, research.

Developer 9/2014 - 9/2015

Developed 22 custom, responsive websites using MODx, HTML, CSS, and JS.

FREELANCER

Owner, etc.

- Ran a small design consulting studio in Gift-Economy.
- Work included: Project Strategy, WordPress Web Development, Branding, UI/UX.

ADLIFE MARKETING

Web Consultant 2014

Built small sites for local businesses at startup. Designer, Sales, Account Management, and Development.

FIDELITY INVESTMENTS

Designer 2013

Designed and developed ads following their design system using Flash, InDesign, and HTML/CSS.

BRADY PEOPLE ID

Graphic Designer

2006 - 2013

- Designed logos to print for an ID company think lanyards and badge holders.
- Managed 2 remote Designers and was trained in LEAN.

EDUCATION

SUNY ONEONTA

Graphic Design B.A.

UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN

EdX MicroMasters, UX Research and Design